<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.simon.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Simon</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Simon</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Simon</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Simon</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxSimonxx</name>
  <summary>Speech Recognition Tool</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Hulpmiddel voor spraakherkenning</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Taligenkänningsverktyg</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Засіб для розпізнавання голосових команд</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxSpeech Recognition Toolxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Simon is the main front end for the Simon open source speech recognition solution. It is a Simond client and provides a graphical user interface for managing the speech model and the commands.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Simon is het hoofdfrontend voor het Simon open source oplossing voor spraakherkenning. Het is een Simond-client en levert een grafisch gebruikersinterface voor het beheren van het spraakmodel en de commando's.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Simon är huvudgränssnittet för taligenkänningslösningen Simon med öppen källkod. Den är en Simond-klient och tillhandahåller ett grafiskt användargränssnitt för att hantera talmodellen och kommandona.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Simon є основною графічною оболонкою комплексу програм з відкритим кодом для розпізнавання мовлення Simon. Програма є клієнтською частиною Simond, вона надає графічний інтерфейс користувача для керування моделлю мовлення та командами.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxSimon is the main front end for the Simon open source speech recognition solution. It is a Simond client and provides a graphical user interface for managing the speech model and the commands.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Simon can execute all sorts of commands based on the input it receives from the server Simond.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Simon kan allerlei soorten commando's uitvoeren gebaseerd op de invoer die het ontvangt uit de server Simond.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Simon kan köra alla sorters kommandon baserat på indata som tas emot från SImond-servern.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Simon може виконувати всі типи команд, заснованих на вхідних даних, які надаються його серверною частиною (Simond).</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSimon can execute all sorts of commands based on the input it receives from the server Simond.xx</li>
      <li>Simon provides a unique do-it-yourself approach to speech recognition. Instead of predefined, pre-trained speech models
       it provides an easy to use end-user interface to create language and acoustic models from scratch.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Simon levert een unieke doe-het-zelf benadering voor spraakherkenning. In plaats van voorgedefinieerde, vooraf getrainde spraakmodellen biedt het een gemakkelijk te gebruiken interface voor de eindgebruiker om taal- en akoestische modellen vanaf niets aan te maken.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Simon erbjuder ett unikt gör-det-själv tillvägagångssätt för taligenkänning. Istället för fördefinierade, förinlärda talmodeller, tillhandahåller det ett enkelt slutanvändargränssnitt för att skapa språk- och akustikmodeller från grunden.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">У Simon передбачено унікальний підхід до розпізнавання мовлення У Simon передбачено простий у користуванні інтерфейс користувача для створення мовних і акустичних моделей «з нуля».</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSimon provides a unique do-it-yourself approach to speech recognition. Instead of predefined, pre-trained speech models it provides an easy to use end-user interface to create language and acoustic models from scratch.xx</li>
      <li>The end-user can easily download created use cases from other users and share his / her own.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">De eindgebruiker kan gemakkelijk reeds gemaakte zaken van andere gebruikers downloaden en de zijne / hare delen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Slutanvändaren kan enkelt ladda ner användarfall skapade av andra användare och dela med sig av sina egna.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Кінцевий користувач може отримати створені іншими користувачами дані, а також поділитися власними даними.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxThe end-user can easily download created use cases from other users and share his / her own.xx</li>
      <li>Command-and-control solutions especially suitable for disabled people.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Oplossingen voor commando-en-besturing speciaal geschikt voor mensen met een beperking.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Kommando- och styrlösningar särskilt lämpade för handikappade.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Інструменти керування, які особливо корисними для людей із особливими потребами.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCommand-and-control solutions especially suitable for disabled people.xx</li>
      <li>Because of its architecture, the same version of Simon can be used with all languages and dialects. One can even mix languages within one model if necessary.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Vanwege deze architectuur kan dezelfde versie van Simon gebruikt worden met alle talen en dialecten. Men kan zelfs talen binnen één model mixen indien nodig.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">På grund av dess arkitektur kan samma version av Simon användas med alla språk och dialekter. Man kan till och med blanda språk inom en modell om nödvändigt.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Через архітектуру комплексу однією версією Simon можна скористатися для всіх мов і діалектів. Якщо потрібно, можна навіть використовувати одну модель для декількох мов.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxBecause of its architecture, the same version of Simon can be used with all languages and dialects. One can even mix languages within one model if necessary.xx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/simon.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">http://kde.org/applications/utils/simon</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=simon</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=simon</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>simon</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
